i don't know if anybody here travels
extensively for work anybody have a job
where they travel extensively yeah you
do yeah what do you do for work sir
i'm a consultant okay
oh okay what's your name sir kayla
caleb
all right caleb the consultant
so
if you're on like caleb and myself maybe
you travel once twice a year two
professional travis like caleb and
myself a favor don't stay home okay a
lot of rules at the airport and you guys
don't know them and then you get in
caleb and i's way we know what we're
doing every weekend caleb you can attest
to this we still are stuck behind a
person still trying to get a 72 ounce
bottle of perk plus on the plane every
weekend everywhere how come why
like it's got to be three ounces we made
that rule a long time ago three ounces
i don't know where you're going need
that much per plus but you got to throw
that away
[Laughter]
and everything called tsa pre-checked
maybe you have it too
tsa pre-check you don't take off shoes
kind of zip right through but every
airport's different so i have to ask
every airplane i'm like does it take off
my belt like only if it's got metal on
it
you mean like every belt never made
that's how it works
now with the metal
it's a belt
i'm not a scarecrow use my pants with a
piece of rope it's beth
[Music]
i don't trust that tsa man
i think we're just lucky at this point
right you see those people like when's
my break they don't care
and then once you're in the airport what
have like you you guys understand the
airport's a public place right you guys
know it's a public place you know that
do you guys know that you know people
can see you and what you're wearing in
the airport do you know that because i
don't think you do i see some things
listen i know air travel is
uncomfortable i get it doesn't mean you
could show up to a public establishment
in your pajama pants and slippers like
you see the people with their house
pillow the adults they take their pillow
from their bed their home pillow out of
the house could you imagine taking your
home pillow
out of the front door of your house
across the front lawn into a car you sit
in a car with your home pillow you drive
all the way to the airport you park the
car you get out you walk into the
airport with your home pillow
because you have a two-hour layover and
god forbid you stand upright for two
hours go i gotta lie down on the floor
of a carpeted public establishment it's
two o'clock in the afternoon let's be
exhausted go ahead lie down yeah right
there right there go ahead no that's
brian right there perfectly fine right
there in front of panda express go ahead
lie down
when did that become acceptable just lie
on the floor your tie line down
want to do it everywhere do it
everywhere a restaurant i'll have a
table for two there for two be about an
hour wait an hour i'll just lie here
that's fine
fully
fully committed to that joke people
fully committed
i didn't have to honestly i could have
pretended to lie down
i could have mimed it i did not get all
the way down
i think it's easy to get up any skinny
jeans it's not but i did it
[Music]